My buddy Kobe, he's probably somewhere in the comments of being a dick to me, and he comes up and he's like, hey man
What are you doing?
I was like, oh, you're stuck and stuck on some sat and he's like, hey, we do that, we do that over here and I was like, what?
What? He's like, hey man, we're stuck right now.
But, what do you mean?
You're stuck and right now, he's like, yeah, he's like, we're stuck right now.
I'm like, what, and I go over there and share a shit.
Here is everybody dropping.
Whether it's been stuck, you know, stuck on $5.
So hey, I'm gonna hit a main clock, which if Tao is listening, fuck you, Tao.
And, you know, like, stuck, you know, really broke the narrative, because prior to that,
Jane, it was, hey, I'm buying Bitcoin, good for me.
And, uh, stuck, Jane really brought it up where he, you buying Bitcoin, good for you.
And, uh, the whole, the whole network, the whole community has, uh, has really cemented what it is for me to believe in Bitcoin.